Jude Lim (Ken Yoong)

MS in Computer Science and Applications

Email: LinkedIn:

lkyoong428@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/jude-lim-9a2612101/

Mobile: Github:

+1703-679-0990 https://github.com/KenLim4337/

Location: Portfolio:

Falls Church, VA https://kenlim4337.github.io/

I recently graduated with a Master of Science in Computer Science and Applications from Virginia Tech focusing on Human Computer Interaction, Data Analytics, and Machine Learning. I also have over three years of industry experience in Front End Development. My passion is developing and designing interfaces that bridge the gap between users and the complex data and software that drive modern systems.

Skills

Hard Skills

Front End Web Development, Data Analytics, Human Computer Interaction, Machine Vision Applications, User Experience, Conversion Rate Optimization, Responsive Web Design, User Acceptance Testing, A/B Testing, Web Analytics, Back End Web Development

Soft Skills

Teamwork, Problem Solving, Attention to Detail, Critical Thinking, Verbal Communication, Written Communication, Adaptability

Technologies

Web Technologies - HTML, CSS, SASS, LESS, Javascript, jQuery, React, Django, Flask, PHP Data and Analytics - MySQL, PostgreSQL, Python, R, Google Analytics, Google Tag Manager Design Tools - Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Invision, Figma, Miro, Balsamiq Other Programming Languages - Python, Java, C#, C Version Control - Git

Languages

English(*Native*), Mandarin(*Intermediate*), Cantonese(*Intermediate*), Bahasa Melayu(*Intermediate*)

Education

2021 - 2023

Master of Science in Computer Science and Applications, Virginia Tech Graduate Certificate in Data Analytics, Virginia Tech

2014 - 2017

Bachelor of Information Technology (Honors), University of Queensland

Publications Co-author

Human-in-the-loop for computer vision assurance: A survey

Engineering Applications of Artificial Intelligence, Volume 123, Part B, 2023

Professional Experience

Research Assistant

August 2021 - Current

Crowd Intelligence Lab, Virginia Tech (Arlington, VA, USA) | Part-time

Designed and developed two full-stack web development projects. Also helped with writing and editing multiple publications.

 Proposed a novel pipeline that combines Al-powered reverse image search and user feedback to discover and cluster images with similar backgrounds.

- Designed and developed Backdrop Explorer, a web-based platform that allows users to search and subsequently sort Civil War portraits based on their background content.
- Redesigned the homepage of Civil War Photo Sleuth, a free, web-based platform and an online community to help identify unknown portraits of soldiers from the American Civil War era (https://doi.org/10.1016/j.engappai.2023.106376).

Frontend Developer (Conversion Rate Optimization)

February 2018 - July 2021

Conversion Kings (Australia) | Full-time

Increased conversion rates and revenue for over 40 national and international brands through the development, maintenance and analysis of over 250 A/B tests and web-pages.

- Developed pixel-perfect, responsive, cross-browser A/B tests and web-pages based on prototypes provided by designers.
- Reduced project turnaround time and missed bugs by 30% within the first half-year by implementing a standardized user acceptance testing process and managing the team surrounding it.
- Slashed training times for various processes by 50% by writing manuals to help on-board new team members.

Frontend Developer

March 2017 - November 2017

Gliding Queensland (Australia) | Freelance

Constructed a framework for the client's redesign efforts by providing feedback based on design and development best practices.

- Fixed existing issues and compiled recommended updates based on user experience principles.
- Documented website functions to help existing members easily access and modify published content.

Intern

December 2015 - February 2016

KPerak Implementation and Coordination Corporation (Malaysia) | Full Time

Delivered a full-stack project in the form of an internal employee assessment web application. The project was completed 2 weeks ahead of schedule and subsequently deployed with minimal rework.

Other Experience

Hacker & Crew

July 2017

GovHack 2017 (Australia)

Received honorable mention for the "Going places" national award category by developing a mobile web application. Also made sure participants were hacking in a safe and comfortable environment by helping set up the event location, providing technical support and preparing meals.

Other Certifications

2020

Advanced Google Analytics, Google Analytics Academy **Google Tag Manager Fundamentals**, Google Analytics Academy

2019

15.071x The Analytics Edge, MITx on edX **Google Analytics for Beginners**, Google Analytics Academy

2014 - 2016

Bachelor of Information Technology, University of Queensland

Hobbies and Interests

Cooking, Coffee Roasting, Embroidery